TIMOTHY HOWARD

- **♀** 37 Winstone Ave, Chartwell, Hamilton, New Zealand
- ☑ timhow38@gmail.com
- **C** 022 587 8266
- https://www.linkedin.com/in/timhow20
- https://timothy-profile.web.app

PERSONAL STATEMENT

Experienced Service Desk Agent with a demonstrated history of working in the higher education industry. Skilled in Sales, Service Desk, Software Installation, Powershell, and Printer Support.

Strong support professional with a (Level 5)

Diploma in Information Technology Technical Support focused in Information Technology from Wintec - Waikato Institute of Technology.

WORK HISTORY

Waikato Institute of Technology

Hamilton, New Zealand Apr 2018 - Apr 2018

Waikato Institute of Technology

Hamilton, New Zealand Jan 2017 - Present

Bed Post

Hamilton, New Zealand Jan 2016 - Dec 2016

Events Assistant

Assisting or presenting events on behalf of multiple Wintec departments.

Service Desk Agent

Providing technical support to Wintec's internal customers.

- Provided customer support to staff and students via phone, email and face-to-face on the service desk. (approx 840 staff and 20,000 students).
- Assisted in the training of new staff on the service desk.
- Logging jobs, elevating tickets and resolving level 1 and 2 issues using Zendesk.
- Supporting staff experiencing issues with Windows, Office software, Outlook, Projectors, Mobile Phones, Company and BYO computers.

Delivery & Sales Person

Sales & Delivery

- In-store sales and product knowledge.
- Office work including invoicing and general phone support.
- Product delivery & setup on site / in-store.

QUALIFICATIONS

Waikato Institute of Technology

Hamilton, New Zealand 2018 - Present

Bachelor of Applied Information Technology

Major: "Web Development" Included Papers:

Year 01:

Information Technology Operations - Fundamentals of Programming and Problem Solving - Professional Practice - Business Systems Analysis and Design - Introduction to Networks - Operating Systems and Systems Support - Database Principles, Technical Support - Object Oriented Programming - Database Modelling and SQL - Mathematics for Information Technology

Year 02:

 $Interpersonal\ Communications - Data\ Visualization - Web\ Development - Cyber\ Security - Web\ Programming - The\ Web\ Environment$

Year 03:

 $\label{thm:proposed_power_power} Human\ Computer\ Interaction\ - Mobile\ Applications\ Development\ -\ Web\ Applications\ Development\ -\ Business\ Essentials\ for\ IT\ Professionals\ /\ Project\ Management$

Industry Placement/Internship

- · Design Factory
- The GIG Peer Tutoring Prototyping

Waikato Institute of Technology

Hamilton, New Zealand 2017 - 2018

Waikato Institute of Technology

Hamilton, New Zealand 2016 - 2017

Waikato Institute of Technology

Hamilton, New Zealand 2015 - 2016

Saint Johns College

Hamilton, New Zealand 2015

- New Zealand Diploma in Information Technology & Technical Support (Level 5)
- New Zealand Certificate in Information Technology (Level 5)
- National Certificate in Computing (Level 3)
- NCEA (Level 2)

TECHNICAL SKILLS

- Restricted Car Licence with 1R endorsements
- CE -Call Centre Support / Remote Support
- Problem analysis and troubleshooting.
- Active Directory -Powershell Interaction
- ReactJS, WebPack, Angular, PHP, HTML5- Web Frameworks
- Event Planning, Management

- Zendesk Support -Logging, Handling and Solving Cases.
- General Software Support Including: Adobe, Office365, Win & Mac and more.
- Employee Training
- VMware Virtualization
- CSS, SASS, JSS Style Scripting

INTERESTS

- · Road Cycling
- Local Quiz Nights

• Web Applications & UI Design

REFEREES

Sanjay Weerasinghe

Manager Technology Services - Waikato Institute of Technology - ITS

☑ sanjay.weerasinghe@wintec.ac.nz

4 274969612

Stewart Hardie

Systems Engineer - Waikato Institute of Technology

• 0278277290